Jane Harman Papers, 1960-1998 (ongoing) (bulk 1993-1998)
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES IV. LEGISLATIVE FILES 1993-98
  - Subject/issues files
    - Defense (Box 103)
      - Defense conversion/dual-use technology issues, 1993-98
        - Dual use (Box 121, Folder 2-4)
        - Fuel cell buyers (Box 121, Folder 5)
        - Los Angeles Economic Development Corporation (Box 121, Folder 6)
        - Reports/reference materials (Box 121)
          - Aerospace Industrial Base Issues 1996 (Box 121, Folder 7)
          - California Assembly Report of the Select Committee on Defense Conversion 1996 (Box 121, Folder 8)
          - Defense Contractors: Pay, Benefits, and Restructuring During Defense Downsizing 1995 (Box 121, Folder 9)
          - The Evolving Structure of the Defense Industry 1996 (Box 122, Folder 1)
          - Industry in Transition: Strategies and Issues for Aerospace & Defense Companies in Southern California 1993 (Box 122, Folder 2)
          - Life After Cutbacks: Tracking California's Aerospace Workers 1996 (Box 122, Folder 3)
          - Pathway to Privatization, an Industry Perspective: Report of the California CEOs' Defense Privatization Task Force 1996 (Box 122, Folder 4)
          - RAND; Defense Spending, Aerospace, and the California Economy 1993; Regional Distribution of Aerospace Procurement Cuts 1994 (Box 122, Folder 5)
        - Technology Reinvestment Program (TRP) (Box 122, Folder 6)
      - Export policy (satellites, supercomputers), 1993-98
        - China hearings (Box 122, Folder 7-9)
        - China satellite export/launch issue (1998) - background (Box 122)
          - Part 1 (Box 122, Folder 10)
          - Part 2 (Box 123, Folder 1-2)
        - Satellite exports (Box 123, Folder 3-7)
        - Supercomputer exports (Box 124, Folder 1-2)
      - Firms
        - Ace Clearwater (Box 124, Folder 3)
        - Aerojet (Box 124, Folder 4)
        - Aerospace Corporation (Box 124, Folder 5-7)
        - Aerospace Corporation/Science Applications International Corporation merger (Box 124, Folder 8)
        - Aerospace industry - general (Box 125, Folder 1)
        - Allied Signal (Box 125, Folder 2)
        - AMCOMP Corporation (Box 125, Folder 3)
        - Applied Solar Energy Corporation (Box 125, Folder 4)
        - Astro Flight (Box 125, Folder 5)
        - bd Systems, Inc. (Box 125, Folder 6)
        - Boeing, [see also Oversize Materials] (Box 125, Folder 7)
        - Computer Sciences Corporation (Box 125, Folder 8)
        - Cosmodyne (Box 125)
          - Part 1 (Box 125, Folder 9-11)
          - Part 2 (Box 126, Folder 1)
        - CVB, Inc. (Box 126, Folder 2)
        - Ducommon Inc. (Box 126, Folder 3)
        - Dyna-Cam Industries (TRP winner) (Box 126, Folder 4)
        - EDEL (Box 126, Folder 5)
        - Eidetics Aircrafts (Box 126, Folder 6)
        - FMS Corporation (Box 126, Folder 7)
        - GDE Systems, Inc. (Box 126, Folder 8)
        - Geodynamics (Box 126, Folder 9)
        - GTE Government Systems (Box 126, Folder 10)
        - Hi-Shear (Box 126, Folder 11)
        - Hitco Technologies (Box 126, Folder 12)
        - Hughes - defense/space (Box 126, Folder 13)
        - Hughes Electronics (Box 127, Folder 1)
        - International Rectifier (Box 127, Folder 2)
        - ITT (Box 127, Folder 3)
        - Lockheed Martin (Box 127, Folder 4)
        - Logicon (Box 127, Folder 5)
        - Magnavox (Box 127, Folder 6)
        - Matrix Science Corp. (Box 127, Folder 7)
        - McDonnell Douglas (Box 127, Folder 8)
        - Microcosm, Inc. (Box 127, Folder 9)
        - Moog, Inc. (Box 127, Folder 10)
        - Mykotronix (Box 127, Folder 11)
        - Norris Industries (Box 127, Folder 12)
        - Northrop Grumman (Box 127, Folder 13)
        - Pacific Applied Research (Box 127, Folder 14)
        - Physical Optics Corp. (Box 127, Folder 15)
        - Precision Echo (Box 128, Folder 1)
        - RAND (Box 128, Folder 2)
        - Raytheon (Box 128, Folder 3)
        - Robotix (Box 128, Folder 4)
        - Rockwell (Box 128, Folder 5)
        - SAIC (Box 128, Folder 6)
        - Teledyne Microelectronics (Box 128, Folder 7)
        - TRW (Box 128, Folder 8-9)
        - Wyatt Technology (Box 128, Folder 10)
      - Hearing transcripts
        - House Committee on Armed Services, An Assessment of the Bottom-Up Review: Hearings before the Military Forces and Personnel Subcommittee of the Committee on Armed Services, House of Representatives, 103rd Cong., 2nd sess., 1994 (Box 129, Folder 1)
        - House Committee on National Security, Hearings on National Defense Authorization Act for Fiscal Year 1998- H.R. 1119 and Oversight of Previously Authorized Programs before the Committee on National Security, House of Representatives, 105th Cong., 1st sess., 1997 (Box 129, Folder 2)
      - Los Angeles Air Force Base (LA AFB), 1993-97
        - Base briefings/fact sheets (Box 129, Folder 3)
        - Base realignment and closure (BRAC) (Box 129)
          - Hearings (Box 129, Folder 4)
          - Information pre-BRAC 1995 (Box 129, Folder 5)
          - Reports/studies (Box 129)
            - Part 1, [see also SERIES IX. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS-Computer media] (Box 129, Folder 6-8)
            - Part 2 (Box 130, Folder 1-2)
          - Miscellaneous correspondence and background (Box 130, Folder 3-6)
        - Letters supporting LA AFB (Box 130)
          - Part 1 (Box 130, Folder 7)
          - Part 2 (Box 131, Folder 1-2)
        - Reuse of bases (Box 131, Folder 3)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 131)
          - General (Box 131, Folder 4)
          - LA AFB & Space and Missile Command (Box 131, Folder 5)
          - News clippings (Box 131, Folder 6)
          - White Point housing (Box 131, Folder 7-8)
      - Missile defense
        - General, 1994-95 (Box 132, Folder 1-4)
        - General, 1996-98 (Box 133, Folder 1-5)
        - HR 3144 - Defend America Act of 1996 (Box 134, Folder 1-2)
        - Reports and background information (Box 134, Folder 3-7)
      - Programs, 1994-98
        - A-12 (Box 135, Folder 1)
        - Advanced Milsatcom (Box 135, Folder 2)
        - Advanced Technology Transit Bus (ATTB) (Box 135, Folder 3)
        - Airborne Laser (ABL) (Box 135, Folder 4)
        - Arrow/THEL (Box 135, Folder 5)
        - Arsenal ship (Box 135, Folder 6)
        - B-1 bomber (Box 135, Folder 7)
        - Battle Combat Identification System (BCIS) (Box 135, Folder 8)
        - C-17 (Box 135, Folder 9-10)
        - Comanche (Box 135, Folder 11)
        - Crusader (Box 135, Folder 12)
        - CVN-77 (Box 135, Folder 13)
        - Electric vehicles (DoD) (Box 136, Folder 1)
        - F-14 (Box 136, Folder 2)
        - F-15 (Box 136, Folder 3)
        - F-16 (Box 136, Folder 4)
        - F-18 (Box 136, Folder 5-8)
        - F-18D sale to Thailand (Box 136, Folder 9)
        - F-22 (Box 136, Folder 10-11)
        - Flat panel displays (Box 137, Folder 1)
        - Global Broadcast System - Hughes (Box 137, Folder 2)
        - Hughes Integrated Synthetic Aperture Radar (HISAR) (Box 137, Folder 3)
        - Hunter UAV - TRW (Box 137, Folder 4)
        - Joint Primary Aircraft Training System (JPATS) (Box 137, Folder 5)
        - Joint Signals Intelligence (SIGINT) Avionics Family (JSAF) (Box 137, Folder 6)
        - Joint Strike Fighter (JSF) (Box 137, Folder 7-8)
        - Joint Surveillance and Tracking Attack Radar System (JSTARS) (Box 137, Folder 9)
        - Land Warrior (Protest) - Hughes (Box 137, Folder 10)
        - Life Support for Trauma and Transport (LSTAT) (Box 137, Folder 11)
        - MILSTAR (Box 137, Folder 12)
        - Miniature Sensor Technology Integration (MSTI) (Box 137, Folder 13)
        - Sea Launch (Box 137, Folder 14)
        - Shortstop (Box 138, Folder 1)
        - Space Based Infrared System (SBIRS) (Box 138, Folder 2)
        - Space Based Laser (SBL) (Box 138, Folder 3)
        - Tactical Tomahawk (Box 138, Folder 4)
        - V-22 (Box 138, Folder 5)
      - Weapons of mass destruction, 1996
        - Counterproliferation and WMD - studies and reports (Box 138, Folder 6-8)
        - HR 3729 - Chem-Bio Defense (Box 139, Folder 1-5)
      - Miscellaneous issues, 1993-98
        - Acquisition reform (Box 139)
          - Part 1, [see also SERIES IX. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS-Computer media] (Box 139, Folder 6-7)
          - Part 2 (Box 140, Folder 1-3)
        - Aerospace Advisory Committee (Box 140, Folder 4)
        - Articles/papers (Box 140, Folder 5)
        - Assembled Chemical Weapons Assessment program (ACWA) letter (Box 140, Folder 6)
        - Blackhawk incident (Box 140, Folder 7)
        - Bosnia (Box 141, Folder 1-6)
        - California issues, miscellaneous (Box 141, Folder 7)
        - California National Guard (Box 141, Folder 8)
        - Civil engineering at LA AFB (Box 141, Folder 9)
        - Coast Guard housing (Box 141, Folder 10)
        - Coast Guard letter (Box 141, Folder 11)
        - Cohen visit, May 1997 (Box 142, Folder 1)
        - Cohen letters (Box 142, Folder 2)
        - Conferences - George Raach (Box 142, Folder 3)
        - Conger Weeklies, Nov 1997-Feb 1998 (Box 142, Folder 4)
        - Danzig, Richard (Box 142, Folder 5)
        - Deep Freeze - Navy (Box 142, Folder 6)
        - Defense (Box 142, Folder 7-10)
        - Elk Hills (Box 142, Folder 11)
        - Fatigue management (Box 142, Folder 12)
        - Federally Funded Research and Development Centers (FFRDCs) (Box 142, Folder 13)
        - Gansler meeting (Box 143, Folder 1)
        - Green Hills, [see also SERIES VIII. PHOTOGRAPHS-Constituent services-Events/district activities] (Box 143, Folder 2)
        - Hammon: district files, strategic plan, Weeklies, Jan 1996 (Box 143, Folder 3-5)
        - Household goods reengineering (Box 143, Folder 6)
        - HR 7 - Contract with America (Box 143, Folder 7)
        - HR 2786 - IMPACT 1997 (Box 143, Folder 8)
        - Intelligence issues (Box 143)
          - CIA - crack in Los Angeles (Box 143, Folder 9)
          - General (Box 143, Folder 10)
          - HPSCI hearings (Box 143, Folder 11)
          - HR 3237 - Intelligence Community Act (Box 143, Folder 12)
          - Information infrastructure (Box 143, Folder 13)
          - Intelligence issues/bill FY 99 (Box 143, Folder 14)
          - Iran-Bosnia report (Box 143, Folder 15)
          - Whistleblower Act (Box 144, Folder 1-2)
        - Interviews (Box 144, Folder 3)
        - Landmines (Box 144, Folder 4)
        - Line item veto (Box 144, Folder 5)
        - Lomita Little League (Box 144, Folder 6)
        - McClellan Air Force Base (Box 144, Folder 7)
        - Mergers of defense firms (Box 144, Folder 8-9)
        - Microwave power tubes (Box 144, Folder 10)
        - Modular Airborne Fire Fighting Systems (MAFFS) (Box 144, Folder 11)
        - Naval Museum - Jim Cross (Box 144, Folder 12)
        - New energy ventures (Box 144, Folder 13)
        - North Korea missiles - Weldon-Spratt bill (Box 144, Folder 14)
        - Nunn-Lugar program (Box 145, Folder 1)
        - Offsets (Box 145, Folder 2)
        - Perry visit to Los Angeles (Box 145, Folder 3)
        - Privatization of depots (Box 145, Folder 4)
        - Quadrennial Defense Review (QDR)/National Defense Panel (NDP) (Box 145, Folder 5-6)
        - Raach exit memo, 29 Aug 1997 (Box 145, Folder 7)
        - Readiness (Box 145, Folder 8)
        - Restructuring charges (Box 145, Folder 9)
        - Southwest Defense Complex (Box 145, Folder 10)
        - Speeches, 1996-98 (Box 145, Folder 11)
        - Stevens, Dr. Bryan (Box 146, Folder 1)
        - Tactical airpower (Box 146, Folder 2)
        - Torrance Jr. ROTC (Box 146, Folder 3)
        - University of California (Box 146, Folder 4)
        - U.S.-Israeli Interparliamentary Commission (Box 146, Folder 5)
        - USS Missouri, berthing (Box 146, Folder 6)
        - Veterans (Box 146)
          - American GI forum - cosponsor (Box 146, Folder 7)
          - Displaced workers (Box 146, Folder 8)
          - Guard and Reserves (Box 146, Folder 9)
          - Gulf War illness (Box 146, Folder 10)
          - Low cost food options for homeless veterans (Box 146, Folder 11)
          - Motion Picture Licensing Association (MPLA) (Box 146, Folder 12)
          - VA hospital - Long Beach (Box 146, Folder 13)
          - Veterans Affairs (Box 146, Folder 14)
          - Veterans' issues (Box 146, Folder 15)
          - VFW rifles (Box 146, Folder 16)
          - Vietnam Veterans of America (VVA) Chapter 53 (Box 146, Folder 17)
    - Women in the armed forces, 1993-98
      - Abortion services for overseas servicewomen (Box 146, Folder 18)
      - Adultery (Box 146, Folder 19)
      - Commission on Military Training and Gender-related Issues (Box 146, Folder 20)
      - Defense Advisory Committee on Women in the Services (DACOWITS) (Box 147, Folder 1)
      - Defense Authorization Act, FY 98-99 (Box 147, Folder 2-3)
      - Flinn, AF Lieutenant Kelly (Box 147, Folder 4)
      - Hale, General David (Box 147, Folder 5)
      - Harman statements/letters/press (Box 147, Folder 6)
      - Integrated/segregated basic training (Box 147)
        - Part 1 (Box 147, Folder 7-9)
        - Part 2 (Box 148, Folder 1)
      - Kassebaum-Baker segregated training report (Box 148, Folder 2-3)
      - Military justice system (Box 148, Folder 4-5)
      - "New Opportunities for Military Women: Effects upon Readiness, Cohesion and Morale" (Oct 1997), RAND (Box 148, Folder 6)
      - Opportunities for women in the military (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - Sexual misconduct investigation
        - Army Senior Review Panel on Sexual Harassment (Box 149, Folder 2-5)
        - Army sexual harassment (Box 149)
          - Part 1 (Box 149, Folder 6)
          - Part 2 (Box 150, Folder 1)
        - General (Box 150, Folder 2-4)
        - Publications and reports (Box 150)
          - CODEL Harman briefing book, Fort Jackson, SC, Jan 1998 (Box 150, Folder 5)
          - Defense Equal Opportunity Council, Report on the Task Force on Discrimination and Sexual Harassment, v. 1 and 2 May 1995 (Box 150, Folder 6)
          - Department of Defense, 1995 Sexual Harassment Survey (Box 151, Folder 1)
          - Department of the Army, Human Relations Action Plan: The Human Dimension of Combat Readiness Jul 1997 (Box 151, Folder 2)
          - General Accounting Office, Military Equal Opportunity: Certain Trends in Racial and Gender Data May Warrant Further Analysis Nov 1995 (Box 151, Folder 3)
          - General Accounting Office, Military Equal Opportunity: Problems with Services' Complaint Systems Are Being Addressed by DoD Jan 1996 (Box 151, Folder 4)
          - General Accounting Office, letter to the Honorable Robert K. Dornan, Chairman, Subcommittee on Military Personnel, 10 Jun 1996 (Box 151, Folder 5)
          - Madeline Morris, "By Force of Arms: Rape, War and Military Culture," Duke Law Journal 45 (1996): 651-781 (Box 151, Folder 6)
          - The Secretary of the Army's Senior Review Panel Report on Sexual Harassment, V. 1&2 Jul 1997 (Box 151, Folder 7-8)
          - Senior Review Panel on Sexual Harassment and DAIG Special Report: TRADOC Update Jan 1998 (Box 151, Folder 9)
          - U.S. Navy, Commander's Handbook: A Toolkit for Prevention of Sexual Harassment 1994 (Box 151, Folder 10)
      - Women in the military - combat exclusion (Box 151, Folder 11-12)
    - General - 103rd, 1993-94
      - Appropriations amendments (Box 152, Folder 1)
      - Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco and Firearms (BATF) bill (Box 152, Folder 2)
      - Dept. of Defense: COLAS, Health care (Box 152, Folder 3-4)
      - Gulf War Syndrome (Box 152, Folder 5)
      - Hubble telescope (Box 152, Folder 6)
      - Legislative agenda, 1993 (Box 152, Folder 7)
      - Legislative printouts (Box 152, Folder 8)
      - National Performance Review (Box 152, Folder 9)
      - Research materials (Box 152, Folder 10)
      - Speeches and clippings (Box 152, Folder 11)
    - General - 104th, 1995-96
      - 104th Legislative Summary (Box 152, Folder 12-13)
      - Affirmative action (Box 153, Folder 1-5)
      - Aviation Security Enhancement (Box 153)
        - Part 1 (Box 153, Folder 6)
        - Part 2 (Box 154, Folder 1)
      - Balancing the budget (Box 154, Folder 2)
      - Budget reform (Cox, et al.) (Box 154, Folder 3)
      - Clean Water Act (Box 154, Folder 4)
      - Clinical Laboratory Improvements Act (CLIA) (Antitrust Health Care Advancement Act of 1976) (Box 154, Folder 5)
      - Coast Guard Authorization (Box 154, Folder 6)
      - Contra-CIA crack cocaine investigation (Box 154, Folder 7)
      - Debt limit (Box 154, Folder 8)
      - Democratic Policy Committee message (Box 154, Folder 9)
      - Dole tax plan (Box 155, Folder 1)
      - Entitlements (Box 155, Folder 2)
      - Farm bill, 1996 (Box 155, Folder 3)
      - Food and Drug Administration reform legislation (Box 155, Folder 4)
      - Foreign Aid Authorization FY 96 (Box 155, Folder 5)
      - HR 748 - Team Act (Gunderson) (Box 155, Folder 6)
      - HR 988 - Attorney Accountability Act (Box 155, Folder 7)
      - HR 994 - Regulatory Reform (Box 155, Folder 8)
      - HR 1058 - Securities Litigation Reform (Box 155, Folder 9-10)
      - HR 1075 - Product Liability Reform (Box 156, Folder 1-2)
      - HR 1162 - Deficit Reduction Lockbox (Box 156, Folder 3-5)
      - HR 1972 - Independent Contractor (Box 156, Folder 6)
      - HR 3396 - Defense of Marriage Act (Box 156, Folder 7)
      - HR 4303 - Bill to reimburse for educating illegal alien children (Box 157, Folder 1)
      - Intelligence Committee (Box 157, Folder 2)
      - Legal Services Corporation, FY 96-97 (Box 157, Folder 3-4)
      - Lobbying Disclosure Act (Box 157, Folder 5)
      - Medicare/Medicaid - False Claims Act Amendments (Box 157, Folder 6)
      - Omnibus appropriations FY 96 (Box 157, Folder 7)
      - Product Liability Conference Report (Box 157, Folder 8)
      - Religious Freedom Amendment (Box 157, Folder 9)
      - Reproductive health (Box 157, Folder 10)
      - Task Force on Immigration Reform (Box 157, Folder 11)
      - Tax cuts bill (Box 157, Folder 12)
      - Technology Reinvestment Program (TRP) (Box 157, Folder 13)
      - Teenage pregnancy (Box 157, Folder 14)
      - Telecommunications reform (Box 157, Folder 15)
      - Term limits (Box 157, Folder 16)
      - Weapons of mass destruction (Box 157)
        - Part 1 (Box 157, Folder 17)
        - Part 2 (Box 158, Folder 1)
      - Women's health - choice (Box 158, Folder 2)
      - Working Families Flexibility Act (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Major legislative initiatives and issues - 105th, 1997-98
      - AIDS Healthcare Foundation (Box 158, Folder 4)
      - Ballona Wetlands flapgates (Box 158, Folder 5)
      - Campaign Finance Reform - Blue Dog proposal (HR 1366) (Box 158)
        - Part 1 (Box 158, Folder 6)
        - Part 2 (Box 159, Folder 1-3)
      - Census 2000 (Box 159, Folder 4)
      - Democratic Coalition (Blue Dog) Budget Proposal, FY 97-98 (Box 159, Folder 5-7)
      - Energy and Water Appropriations, FY 98-99 (Box 159)
        - Part 1 (Box 159, Folder 8)
        - Part 2 (Box 160, Folder 1)
      - Fair Housing Amendment - residential care facilities (Box 160, Folder 2)
      - Fast Track Trade Authority (Box 160)
        - Part 1 (Box 160, Folder 3-6)
        - Part 2 (Box 161, Folder 1-3)
      - HR 695 - Security and Freedom Through Encryption Act of 1997 (Box 161, Folder 4-5)
      - HR 2400 - Building Efficient Surface Transportation and Equity Act (BESTEA) (Box 161, Folder 6)
      - HR 3206 - Special Needs Housing (Box 162, Folder 1-5)
      - Intermodal Surface Transportation Efficiency Act (ISTEA) op-ed (Box 163, Folder 1)
      - ISTEA reauthorization (Box 163, Folder 2-5)
      - Lockbox FY 98 (Box 163, Folder 6)
      - Machal resolution (HConRes 268) (Box 164, Folder 1)
      - National Days of Dialogue (HConRes 195) (Box 164, Folder 2)
      - Ninth Circuit split (Box 164, Folder 3)
      - POW-MIA flag (Box 164, Folder 4-6)
      - Redondo Beach - Edison plant (Box 165, Folder 1)
      - Russia-Iran proliferation (Box 165, Folder 2)
      - South Bay Regional Communication Authority (SBRCA) - FCC filing (Box 165)
        - Part 1 (Box 165, Folder 3-6)
        - Part 2 (Box 166, Folder 1)
      - State Children's Health Insurance Program (S-CHIP) vaccinations (Box 166, Folder 2)
      - Title XVI - wastewater recycling (Box 166, Folder 3-4)
      - Western Regional Law & Technology Center (Box 166, Folder 5-7)
    - General - 105th, 1997-98
      - 105th Congress legislative summary (Box 167, Folder 1)
      - 105th Congress membership list (Box 167, Folder 2)
      - Floor statements (Box 167, Folder 3)
      - Talking points (Box 167, Folder 4-7)
      - 245(i) INS (Box 167, Folder 8)
      - AIDS health care issues (Box 167, Folder 9)
      - American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE) (Box 168, Folder 1)
      - AMTRAK (Box 168, Folder 2)
      - Asset forfeiture (Box 168, Folder 3)
      - Auburn Dam (Box 168, Folder 4)
      - Auto insurance reform (Box 168, Folder 5)
      - Balanced Budget Agreement FY 98 (Box 168, Folder 6)
      - Balanced Budget Amendment (Box 168, Folder 7)
      - Bankruptcy reform (Box 168, Folder 8)
      - Base closure economic impact analysis - GAO draft report (Box 168, Folder 9)
      - Bay Delta (Box 168, Folder 10)
      - Bilingual education (Box 168, Folder 11)
      - Blue Dog Democrats (Box 168, Folder 12)
      - Budget Reconciliation Conference Report - FY 98 (Box 168, Folder 13)
      - Budget reform (Box 168, Folder 14)
      - Cable television issues (Box 168, Folder 15)
      - California Farm Bureau (Box 168, Folder 16)
      - Campaign finance reform (Box 169, Folder 1-4)
      - Census information (Box 169, Folder 5)
      - Chevron refinery - El Segundo (Box 169, Folder 6)
      - Child care - President's proposal (Box 169, Folder 7)
      - Church of Scientology (Box 169, Folder 8)
      - Chynoweth, W. Edward, "Women at West Point and All That" 1996 (Box 169, Folder 9)
      - Citizen's Protection Act - Commerce-Justice-State appropriations (Box 170, Folder 1)
      - City of Los Angeles federal issues (Box 170, Folder 2)
      - Class action reform (Box 170, Folder 3)
      - Clean water initiatives (Box 170, Folder 4)
      - Clear air regulations (Box 170, Folder 5-6)
      - Clinton scandal (Box 170, Folder 7)
      - Coalition Budget FY 98 (Box 170, Folder 8)
      - Comp Time Flexibility Act (Box 170, Folder 9)
      - Contract blacklisting (Box 170, Folder 10)
      - Copyright extension/music licensing (Box 171, Folder 1)
      - Co-sponsorship requests (Box 171, Folder 2)
      - CPI adjustment (Box 171, Folder 3)
      - Davis-Bacon (Box 171, Folder 4)
      - Death taxes (Box 171, Folder 5)
      - Deficit reduction/balanced budget (Box 171, Folder 6)
      - Del Amo Action Committee (Box 171, Folder 7)
      - Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee (Box 171, Folder 8)
      - Democratic Leadership Council (Box 171, Folder 9)
      - Dolphins and tuna (Box 171, Folder 10)
      - Economic diversification project (Box 171, Folder 11)
      - Educational Advisory Committee (Box 171, Folder 12)
      - Education issues (Box 171, Folder 13)
      - El Niño (Box 171, Folder 14)
      - Electrical deregulation (Box 171, Folder 15)
      - Environmental issues (Box 171, Folder 16)
      - Evolution of a balanced budget agreement (Box 171, Folder 17)
      - Flag protection (Box 172, Folder 1)
      - Foreign Trade Zones (Box 172, Folder 2)
      - Gasoline taxes (Box 172, Folder 3)
      - Gay rights issues (Box 172, Folder 4)
      - GOP tax cuts analysis (Box 172, Folder 5)
      - Gov. Wilson Conference for Women (Box 172, Folder 6)
      - High Tech issues (Box 172, Folder 7)
      - Housing policy (Box 172, Folder 8)
      - HR 2 - Public Housing Reform (Box 172, Folder 9)